<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TubesHotel-U</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">CLose</string>

    <string name="titledescjayakarta">Description</string>
    <string name="mapjayakartabdg">Bandung,West Java</string>
    <string name="maindescjayakarta">
        Description:
        \n\n
        The Jayakarta Suites Bandung is a magnificently located hotel and resort.It is perched above the highland city of Bandung, providing sweeping views of the entire city and surrounding mountains.

Beautiful view rooms and suites are available for your accommodation in Bandung, with all the facilities of a four-star hotel. Guests of The Jayakarta Suites Bandung will enjoy famous Indonesian Hospitality and outstanding services.

We attract you a tour to the local tea plantations or play around of golf at the nearby Golf Course, then relax at the end of the day in hotel’s bar or restaurant to enjoy the romantic evening in Bandung.</string>
    <string name="maindescjayakartajkt"> Description:
        \n\n
       Designed as a business hotel, The Jayakarta SP Jakarta Hotel  Spa provides rooms and facilities to fulfill your MICE needs, it also completed with entertainment and leisure facilities to accommodate your needs for refreshing and relaxing. The Jayakarta SP Jakarta Hotel Spa offer a fully facilitated hotel for you who
        expect both business and leisure activity.
        \n\n
Closed to Jakartas old city, now being gradually restored to its former glory, and with easy access to all parts of the city via the city busway system, Jl. Hayam Wuruk makes both a convenient and fascinating base for both tourist and business people alike.

Business and leisure travelers seeking the many up-market comforts of a top-quality hotel will find all these and more at our four-stars The Jayakarta SP Jakarta Hotel Spa, where world-class standards of service are seamlessly. Finally we welcome you to Jakarta.</string>
    <string name="activity">Activity</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
